SUDISHA MISHRA

Content Editor

+91-99-585-20226 sudisha.misra95@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/sudisha-content/ sudishamishra.com

ABOUT

I'm a 25-year-old Content Editor with nearly six years experience in creating custom and specialized content. Competent in writing and editing high quality content and curating effective marketing strategies while displaying confidence and professionalism at all times.

EXPERIENCE

CONTENT EDITOR

AdPushup | Dec 2019 - Present

- Increased blog pageviews from 130k to 210k within 3 quarters.
- Single-handedly increased average newsletter open rate from 6.5% to 12%.
- Managed a content team of 4 content specialists.
- Introduced newer content forms in the blog.

SENIOR CONTENT WRITER

IndustryARC | Feb 2019 - Oct 2019

- Promoted to Team Mentor within 2 months of joining.
- Created 5 long content pieces per week along with editing 15 simultaneously.

BUSINESS ASSOCIATE

Bank of Baroda | June 2018 - Jan 2019

- Managed Operations department alone in an semiurban branch.
- Involved in Credit Operations as a clerk (otherwise reserved for officers).

INTERN

The Hindu | Dec 2015 - Jan 2016

- Covered news related to press conferences and medical camps held during Chennai floods.
- Got two major news articles published in the main newspaper

SENIOR CORRESPONDENT AND EDITOR

DUBeat | Dec 2014 - May 2016

- Promoted to Senior Correspondent within 6 months of joining.
- Became core editor and managed a team of 40 writers and photographers.

SKILLS

- Team management
- Flexibility
- Content specialization: Textual, graphic, video
- Content Marketing
- Growth Strategies

SOFTWARE/TOOLS

- Adobe Premier Pro (self-taught)
- Adobe Lightroom
- SEMRush
- Google Analytics
- Google Search Console
- WordPress
- Hubspot
- Mailchimp
- Canva
- Microsoft Office
- Google Suite

EDUCATION

IGNOU

2019 - Present

MA in English Literature

DELHI UNIVERSITY

2013-2016

BA (Hons.) in English Literature (First division)